We often hear about team building.
我们经常听到关于团队建设的话题。
Some companies hire team-building gurus to give us lectures on how to collaborate more productively.
一些公司会聘请团队建设专家来给我们讲授如何更高效地相互协作。
They also organise awaydays – time that employees spend together away from their normal workplace.
他们还会组织外出活动日——员工们离开日常工作场所一起度过的时光。
Here in the UK, employees can take part in activities such as Zombie boot camps where military instructors train you how to fight walking 'dead people'.
在英国，员工们可以参加诸如僵尸训练营之类的活动，在那里军事教官会训练你如何与“行尸走肉”战斗。
For the brainier office workers amongst us there are crime investigations modelled on popular TV dramas like Sherlock Holmes and CSI.
对于我们当中更聪明的办公室职员来说，还有以《神探夏洛克》和《犯罪现场调查》等热门电视剧为蓝本的犯罪调查活动。
Stressed-out city workers might have ukulele lessons made available to them.
心力交瘁的城市上班族可能会有机会参加尤克里里课程。
Why is that a good team-building exercise?
为什么这是一项很好的团队建设活动呢？
Ukulele teacher Lorraine Bow says: "The fact that they can play a musical instrument within an hour is quite a fulfilling thing, really.
尤克里里老师洛林·鲍说：“他们能在一小时内学会弹奏一种乐器，这真的是一件很有成就感的事。
It's not competitive – it's quite easy to do and a bit less intimidating than a guitar..."
这没有竞争性，很容易做到，而且比弹吉他少了点令人生畏的感觉……”
Actually, a horse might be a bit more intimidating than an instrument.
实际上，一匹马可能比一种乐器更令人生畏。
The animals are used by a company in Abu Dhabi which teaches leadership through horse training.
阿联酋阿布扎比的一家公司利用马匹通过训练马的方式来教授领导力。
Basically, you have to go in a yard with a horse and persuade it that you're the boss by using body language.
基本上，你要和一匹马进入一个院子，然后通过肢体语言让它相信你是老大。
Kelly Eide, co-founder of True Leadership, says: "The horses don't care if your hair is purple, if you're a man or a woman, if you're old or young... It transcends all of those cultural boundaries - age, gender, religion, tradition etc. - so that's a perfect fit.
“真实领导力”公司的联合创始人凯利·艾迪说：“马不在乎你的头发是不是紫色的，不在乎你是男是女，不在乎你是老是少……它超越了所有这些文化界限——年龄、性别、宗教、传统等等——所以这非常合适。
And in an organization where you really need groups of people to gel, who come from backgrounds which have no common norms, you can teach that most efficiently with a horse."
在一个组织里，你真的需要来自不同背景、没有共同准则的一群人能够融洽相处，用马可以最有效地教会他们这一点。”
And the horse feels instinctively whether or not you are a natural leader.
马能本能地感觉到你是否是天生的领导者。
So if after you've done a good presentation your boss offers you a carrot, you'll know where he might have learnt it from.
所以，如果你做了一场精彩的展示后老板给你奖励，你就知道他可能是从哪里学来这一招的了。